Tuesday June 20, 2023. Who have the implications for pastor from various church to the Phil jars?
Thank you Mayor as I was sitting here and looked at this sign that my first time being in a district part
is it's Miami talking about your signing up there having spirit opportunity envisioned
and I just want to say that, look around up most of you all the parking heads.
And i really feel good about where we are right now as administration this time
.
We...I'd like us on a prayer for God gives me the wisdom encourage
To lead
With
The
Collective
...
..
Wisdom
One with another
That can bring our community back what it once was in greater
So if he would bow
with me father we thank you for leadership
I understand Lord from your word that good
Leadership is a blessing to the lord and bad
It's definitely brings curse on people
So Father, ask God
You just annoy each one of these leaders
The heads whether it has administrative legal whatever
These council members represent their
Constituents Lord
We need this asked god
God, give us wisdom to lead
Guide and direct
And Lord make my end of the best thing it can be in your hands
In Your name
...
Amen
Thank you
...
So mayer
On the claims list
This particular meeting on page 3
Under
The pollution control section there is
An invoice therefore needs
Comprehend
Which was installed pre-engineering
Root
For 27,788
I would recommend
Council pull that one out of
Claims and vote for it separately to avoid any conflict
Okay
They'll be all out of Nice
Cool Man
Looking for Moshin on the rest
The claim
So, just to approve
The sign
Aye
Okay
Then we'd like motion
局
To improve
Distraction
Claim
For pen
On My Commercial
And I'm going
Comprehend
six minutes from June 5th 2020 to regular meeting.
Second,
hi
Hi
December
Parker
five
seven
DL Stacken Edmunds and Palmer Colleen for GERDI
relaxing seeing the amount of $810
May I remember your counsel?
Uh this claim is
four
services rendered
From April 20
To may 12
Um
With
This claim, if approved it would leave a balance in that budgeted and
the budget of $378.84 so obviously there's money
enough to be available for this I'd ask you approval
from your $8010 which was primarily services
responding emails as well
staff
Thank you.
Okay, except it's a power line relocation on 520th road utility easemips from Auto County rural water district Ricky at least he apes James Franklin and Catherine Louise Williams
Herium, herum. E in standard of price and Steven Earl Hodge
My name is Jason Halle I'm from Wilson we were here a couple months ago to kick off this project
We've obtained these easemips for you at no cost
And trying get signature on those as well
As got the utility room before The County
We also need some signatures and I'll still get no rise so we ask the two
On that one is our last county
Could you just approve this one or The next one
Any question for anyone?
Is there a right way at No cost, does it have any norm
You are very good yards to accommodate their want of fishes in desires
Second
Aye
E set
No, a power line relocation 520th road utility relocation agreement with Oklahoma Department of Transportation Oedock and Auto County Commissioner
But this together on the estimate we need to assign it in the county so you can get your project
That's for me.
Second
Hi
Thank You
Those fees all that they give reimbursement
All of you
Everything right
And want all that all the public
Your eyes out and teach
Yeah, some big deal
We did emergency and a lot for emergency purchases according to section 2-33 bit process
Emergency purchases at these solid waste transfer station
Brian Brassfield
The emergency purchases according to section 2-33 bit process
Emergency purchases 1 a solid waste transfer station
Give you little background we are requesting
To get your approval on the emergency status
Just be able
We have more flexibility in completing fire and remediation
While within today's time of wastewater
The solid waste department separately since in losses on June 7
Due to the fire
Facility will not be able
To take personal advice from citizens until after June 22
We were thinking about pushing back another week
Continue picking up trash during all this time
Sending loads out of the more land full side
Fire radiation
The fire was in the building
Was wiring, lights
Dorm motors to control doors
Insulation
Possible roof issues
Some burnt places
In one of those I saw the loader
And possible spripped or system issues
As far as equipment goes
The loader was completely towed
And that solid waste best loader
It is in the fire
They are currently using a backup loader
Another one who's previously ordered and we actually just got it at
But, another back up loaded would be essential to operations
So solving ways needs flexibility
To expedite purchases
It may be possible in the same instances
If they do not impede a safe working environment
Excellent service lines and standard flow of revenue
So we need to get your approval
We can work, it thanks down as there going through this patch, fetching issues
This money already budgeted
Is that who claims
Get us, no, but
We have to get, we just set the money
And not let it go
We'll shake up values and loader
I come in 8000, so check the nature
So if you give this emergency status
Where's your money going from?
The reinforcement checks start for a while
Right there will be any day fun
I have the other ones, so we can't tell you that
So Tyler would be able to
To fluctuate his projects
Which changes this cash will get
And he could use a cash from
Then being able
He should put in the cover for insurance
Right now
We did it
For public works, building
My impede business is usual with the city
With forest things that broke down and couldn't get anything done
How does it compare
What this? I mean, we need to declare
This an emergency
The transfer station
We can not go through normal process
Some of our things would might be able
To a situation where its going
And if I hold up one of the issues, maybe electricians
If we can't get something for them quickly
We might be able to do it down
But just need a place and build another touch
Just make sure that you could give it time
So great in there this
Melting water inside the pond
To plant out the steel layer
Electrical winders like melding outside
It's not often being paid for share of ammo
So I know right now we're not letting the public in
Would this prolong that?
Yes, for paying about to
We are going over and at least by everything
About trying it
For next Friday
And then our travels once again
Our thing is
They've barricaded down all of their shield
That room off
So there's a lot of contact
As far as they can get into the city
Playing the good according to this package
Both of you are invited for some
The new loader came in
So, look at our backup order
You guys had two loaders?
Yes
Now we have 2 loaders again
And when your turn they use it and even know that just come in
Yeah, so one week, back up
Backup was done
That's why I could sit there
But then we were using currently
Was going be coming
So now we're going to have a brand new one that's available
The idea was using the entrance building
To replace those other liables
But then how has it come in this emergency status
And being sent down on the lower
Now, there are just two sort of things
This emergency status is more about
Be able get transportation open
That's also possible because thats all I've seen
We don't want public
This could be a problem with solid waste
So we will absolutely, firstly responsible
Every purchase that you may can when
We get quotes or built to the storage data process
But it comes in being able
To open so
You want back quickly
Backup quickly
It'll become more balanced
The other day I went out and see Kevin discuss some things
All of those are just briefly
There were more loads of drivers
Bring him in and get the turn away
So you know I mean maybe we could be able to
But if we have the ability
It just can't be available
Then where it's needed with use
That weren t not working but two different kinds
Is there any kind a cap on this?
Like what they spend emergency, what
Or does that make sense
I mean it's still everything is going to go through
In a criminal process
So its not that we are giving them like check
We can just throw out an execute
And then they will be talking about all the
Actually, you have provided an absolute detailed report
On every acquisition
Every acquisition and standard
The department on this
Are just saying, oh
Honestly
A little more arguments than the standard process
Personally I don't enjoy to avoid it
Because there really is a bit of time consuming
But because we do not have
Wait for an example
That process or put out the bid and wait for minutes
We can quickly
It's probably going work
So its our trash back up
Are still
Is this starting?
Is it safe to go into?
I mean there is no issues of that
As far as I understand, and know why
It's not ideal
Obviously i think increases risk
Especially the dark life of light
But if wasn t deemed unsafe
Just not necessary
Because we like to be
And theres a real issue
Its all in couldvying
Not only talking about coming down
3 of them coming in there
2 went into the same
1 out on this peer goes to that level
And then after a little bit
When you see one, it's not over all
All those tail-out of their services
Next two come and we've seen
So trash can
Came in
In burn the trash facility
Three best bandits
Which would have been a lot
Can't identify
And you said the sprinklers did not work
So it could be a better problem
Just tell me if I told that
It's packed in where they come down
We can take images
You know, bring them to another
Spector
Think of their dark life
That is what i was so like different
Yeah thats all we don t mean
We love it for a new sprinkler company
Well see what is turned out
But you know, its not up to that all
It isn t interesting
That wouldn't be timex I don nd i told this story
Another idea we hear them call the fire track some fire
Fire track on the parking lot
One of those black brakes
You can say they are already wrecked
Thats gonna stay in trash pan
Is went down and got fired truck too
And he did very much
We need to probably start making some amendments
To the raccoons in our percentage
Were they that once involved
In last one too, we will never know
Are you sure?
I m like emotion
Second
Hi
Parker
Hello new business man
Which is residence of the post office agenda
12 staff reports
13 justi community announcements
14 this meeting would be continued from the council chambers
And staff room for the purpose of executive session
Packer agenda on 16 is a regular scheduled meeting
I m sick count